NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Legal Case File, 1915-1967 (Box 176-264)
  - Thomas v. Mississippi (civil right protest demonstrations, Miss.; "Mississippi Freedom Riders") (Box 252)
    - Related cases (Box 253)
      - Silver v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Simms v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Singleton, H. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Singleton, R. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Smith, L. v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Smith, W. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Steward v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Stoner v. Mississippi, 1964
      - Taylor, J. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Taylor, W. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Thomas, Cecil v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Thomas, Clarence v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Thomas, Willie v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Thompson, J. v. Mississippi, 1963 (Box 259)
      - Thompson, S. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Thornton v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Thurman v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Toombs v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Townsend v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Uphoff v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Vance v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Wagoner v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Watts, T. v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Watts, J. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - White v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Wilson v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Wolfson v. Mississippi, 1962
      - Wright, C. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Wright, L. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Young, P. v. Mississippi, 1963
      - Zuchman v. Mississippi, 1962
  - Thompson v. Portwood, 1952 (education, Tex.) (Box 260)
  - Tinsley v. City of Richmond, 1961 (criminal law, Va.)
  - Tomlinson v. Selective Serv. Draft Bd., 1948 (armed forces, Pa.)
  - Trafton v. Burgges, 1954 (elections, N.C.)
  - Troullier v. Procter, 1954 (education, Okla.)
  - Trujillo v. Garley, undated (elections, N. Mex.)
  - Trustees of Monroe Ave. Church v. Perkins, 1947 (housing, Ohio)
  - Tudor v. Board of Educ., 1953 (education, N.Y.)
  - Tureaud v. Board of Supervisors of La. State Univ., 1953 (education, La.)
  - Turner v. Keefe, 1943 (education, Fla.)
  - Turner v. Warner & Swasey Co., 1942 (labor, Ohio)
  - Tyson v. Byrd, 1949 (education, Md.)
  - Unger v. Dewalt, 1941 (housing, Pa.)
  - United States v. Brandt, 1954 (criminal law, Ohio)
  - United States ex rel. Rogers v. Cummings, 1956 (criminal law, Conn.)
  - United States v. Mortgage Conference, 1948 (housing, N.Y.)
  - United States ex rel. Goldsby v. Wiggins, 1957 (criminal law, Miss.)
  - Valle v. Stengel, 1949 (recreation, N.J.)
  - Vann v. Toledo Metro. Hous. Auth., 1953 (housing, Ohio)
  - Venable v. City of Creve Coeur; City of Creve Coeur v. Deilman, 1956 (housing, Mo.)
  - Ventre v. Ryder, 1959 (elections, La.)
  - Vickers v. Chapel Hill City Bd. of Educ., 1960 (education, N.C.)
  - Virginia v. Billups, 1952 (education, Va.) (Box 261)
  - Virginia v. Carolina Coach Co., 1950 (transportation, Va.)
  - Virginia v. Simms, 1951 (transportation, Va.)
  - Virginia v. Wilson, 1953 (transportation, Va.)
  - Walker v. Board of Educ.; Anderson v. Board of Educ. (education, N.J.; "Englewood School Case")
    - Correspondence and background material, 1954
    - Legal documents, 1954
      - 1 of 3
      - 2 of 3
      - 3 of 3
  - Walker v. Board of Regents of Univ. of Tex., 1954 (education, Tex.) (Box 262)
  - Walker v. Shaw, 1961-1963 (recreation, S.C.)
  - Ward v. Board of Educ., undated (education, Tenn.)
  - Ward v. Chicago & E. Ill. R.R., 1951 (transportation, Ill.)
  - Ward v. Columbus Metro. Hous. Auth., 1954-1955 (housing, Ohio)
  - In re Ware, 1958-1959 (education, N.Y.)
  - Watts v. Housing Auth., 1952-1956 (housing, Ala.)
  - Webster v. City of Birmingham, 1963-1965 (civil rights protest demonstrations, Ala.)
  - Weiss v. Leaon, 1949-1950 (housing, Mo.)
  - Wells v. Dyson, 1955 (education, La.)
  - Westley v. Iberville Parish School Bd., 1953 (education, La.)
  - White v. Smith, 1955 (education, Tex.)
  - Whitmore v. Southern Pac. Co., 1951 (transportation, Calif.) (Box 263)
  - Whitmore v. Stillwell, 1955 (education, Tex.)
  - Whitmyer v. Lincoln Parish School Bd., 1954 (education, La.)
  - Whitus v. Georgia, 1961 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - Williams v. Carolina Coach Co., 1953 (transportation, Va.)
  - Williams v. City of Kansas City, 1951-1953 (recreation, Mo.)
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Williams v. Glasco, 1949 (criminal law, N.J.)
  - Williams v. Hilton Hotels Corp., 1958 (public accommodations, Tex.)
  - Williams v. Hot Shoppes, Inc., 1960 (public accommodations, D.C.)
  - Williams v. Illinois, 1951 (criminal law, Ill.)
  - Williams v. McClellan, 1953 (miscellaneous, Calif.)
  - Williams v. Prather, 1955 (education, La.)
  - Willis v. Walker, 1955 (education, Ky.)
  - Wilson v. Beebe; Johnson v. Beebe, 1951 (education, Del.) (Box 264)
  - Wilson v. Board of Supervisors of La. State Univ., 1950 (education, La.)
  - Wilson v. Bossier Constr. Co., 1954 (housing, La.)
  - Wilson v. Paducah Junior College, 1949-1953 (education, Ky.)
  - Woodbridge v. Housing Auth. (housing, Ind.)
    - Background material, 1952-1953, undated
    - Legal documents, 1952-1953, undated
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
  - Woodruff v. Village of Port Chester, 1951 (criminal law, N.Y.)
  - Woods v. Murrah, 1956 (recreation, Ga.)
  - Woods v. Stone, 1949 (education, Tex.)
  - Worthy v. Foster, 1948 (criminal law, Ga.)
  - Worthy v. Louisville & Nashville R.R., 1948 (transportation, N.Y.)
  - Yoshida v. Gelbert Improvement Co., 1946 (housing, Pa.)
  - Young v. Chicago Hous. Auth., 1952 (labor, Ill.)
  - Youngblood v. Snow, 1955 (recreation, Fla.)
  - Zorach v. Clauson, 1952 (education, N.Y.)
- Restricted (Box R1-R55)
  Correspondence, memoranda, legal documents, and related material removed from the open portion of the collection.
  Folders are organized and described according to the series and container from which they were removed.
  - Office File (Box R1)
    - Amaker, Norman, 1964 (Container 1, folder 1)
    - Board of Directors, 1950-1954 (Container 1, folder 2)
    - Briggs, Lorraine, 1953-1956 (Container 1, folder 4)
    - Byrd, Daniel Ellis
      - Expenses, 1955-1962 (Container 2, folder 1)
    - Carson, Loftus
      - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Container 2, folder 3)
    - Carter, Robert L.
      - Correspondence
        - 1944-1946 (Container 2, folder 6)
        - 1947-1949 (Container 2, folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous legal matters, 1955-1956, undated (Container 2, folder 13)
    - Chisolm, Elwood
      - Speaking engagements, 1955-1957 (Container 3, folder 10)
    - Clerical staff, 1950-1957 (Container 3, folder 14)
    - Cox Committee, hearings on charitable organizations, 1952 (Container 7, folder 20)
    - Davis, John W.
      - Palmetto Education Association (S.C.), 1954-1957 (Container 10, folder 3)
      - Teacher Information and Security Department
        - 1954 Nov.-1955 May (Container 10, folder 8)
        - 1955 June-1955 Dec. (Container 10, folder 9)
        - 1956 (Container 10, folder 10)
        - 1960 (Container 11, folder 1) (Box R2)
    - Finances
      - Contributions, 1951-1952 (Container 12, folder 7)
      - Field Foundation
        - Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Container 12, folder 9)
      - Ford Foundation, grant application, 1951-1953
        - 2 of 3 (Container 12, folder 11)
        - 3 of 3 (Container 12, folder 12)
      - Fund-raising
        - Correspondence
          - 1955-1956 (Container 13, folder 1)
          - 1957-1958 (Container 13, folder 2)
      - Seitz, Howard, 1952-1954 (Container 13, folder 4)
    - Greenberg, Jack
      - Committee on Relationship with NAACP, 1961-1962, undated (Container 13, folder 10)
      - Correspondence
        - 1952-1954 (Container 13, folder 11)
    - Hall, Carsie, 1956-1957 (Container 14, folder 5)
    - Legal staff applications
      - 1945-1949 (Container 15, folder 12)
      - 1950 (Container 15, folder 13) (Box R3)
      - 1951-1953 (Container 15, folder 14)
      - 1956-1963 (Container 15, folder 15)
    - Madison, Waite, 1956-1958 (Container 16, folder 4)
    - Marshall, Thurgood
      - Korean trip
        - Case notes, 1951 (Container 18, folder 6)
    - Mitchell, Clarence, 1948-1954 (Container 26, folder 5)
    - NAACP
      - Southwest Regional Office
        - Correspondence
          - Arkansas, 1952-1953 (Container 28, folder 11)
    - Receipts, 1961 (Container 30, folder 9)
  - Subject File
    - Air Force
      - Hamilton, J. C., 1950-1954 (Container 38, folder 4)
      - Huffman, Vivian, 1955 (Container 38, folder 5)
      - General correspondence
        - 1950-1951 (Container 38, folder 6)
        - 1952 (Container 38, folder 7)
        - 1953 (Box R4)
          - "B-E" (Container 38, folder 8)
          - "F-W" (Container 38, folder 9)
        - 1954
          - "B-F" (Container 38, folder 10)
          - "G-M" (Container 38, folder 11)
          - "S-W" (Container 38, folder 12)
        - 1955 (Container 39, folder 1)
        - 1956-1959 (Container 39, folder 2)
      - Johnson, Casey, 1954 (Container 39, folder 4)
      - Johnson, John J., 1954-1956 (Container 39, folder 5)
      - Lee, Shade M., 1950-1960 (Container 39, folder 6)
      - Stewart, Harry T., and Gordon M. Rapier, 1955-1956 (Container 39, folder 8)
      - Summerford, John W., 1955 (Container 39, folder 9)
    - Armed forces
      - Camps
        - General correspondence
          - 1949-1950 (Container 40, folder 7)
          - 1951 (Container 40, folder 8) (Box R5)
          - 1952-1953 (Container 40, folder 9)
          - 1954 (Container 41, folder 1)
          - 1955-1957 (Container 41, folder 2)
      - General files
        - 1952 (Container 42, folder 1)
        - 1954, correspondence (Container 42, folder 4)
        - 1955 (Container 42, folder 6)
        - 1956 (Container 42, folder 7)
        - 1957 (Container 42, folder 8)
        - 1958 (Box R6)
          - 1 of 3 (Container 42, folder 9)
          - 2 of 3 (Container 42, folder 10)
          - 3 of 3 (Container 42, folder 11)
        - 1959
          - 1 of 3 (Container 43, folder 1)
          - 2 of 3 (Container 43, folder 2)
          - 3 of 3 (Container 43, folder 3)
        - 1960
          - 1 of 2 (Container 43, folder 4)
          - 2 of 2 (Container 43, folder 5)
        - 1961, (Container 43, folder 6)
      - Hugley, John L., 1958 (Container 43, folder 7)
      - National Guard
        - Correspondence, 1951 (Container 43, folder 11)
      - Volman, Violet, 1952-1954 (Container 44, folder 5)
    - Brown, Louis, 1953-1954 (Container 45, folder 6)
    - Casey, Alberta (Box R7)
      - 1952-1953 (Container 45, folder 7)
      - 1954
        - 1 of 2 (Container 45, folder 8)
        - 2 of 2 (Container 45, folder 9)
      - 1955
        - 1 of 2 (Container 46, folder 1)
        - 2 of 2 (Container 46, folder 2)
    - Crime
      - Allen, Lawrence, 1953-1954 (Container 50, folder 3)
      - Anderson, John, 1951 (Container 50, folder 4)
      - Anthony, George, 1950-1955 (Container 50, folder 6)
      - Bailey, George, 1953 (Container 50, folder 7)
      - Bell, Nathan, 1949 (Container 50, folder 8) (Box R8)
      - Belpre, Guillermo, 1950-1952 (Container 50, folder 9)
      - Bey, Irving Morris, 1950-1954 (Container 50, folder 10)
      - Black, James, 1950-1952 (Container 50, folder 11)
      - Brown, Monroe, 1950-1955 (Container 51, folder 3)
      - Brown, William P., 1948-1952 (Container 51, folder 4)
      - Burnette, Clarence, 1951-1954 (Container 51, folder 5)
      - Bryant, David, 1948-1955 (Container 51, folder 6)
      - Carey, Zack, 1950-1955 (Container 51, folder 7)
      - Cook, Cary T., 1949-1956 (Container 51, folder 11)
      - Cross, Alline, 1959 (Container 51, folder 12)
      - Crowe, Burton, 1952-1954 (Container 51, folder 13)
      - Croxton, Robert, 1948-1955 (Container 51, folder 14)
      - Cummings, John, 1953 (Container 51, folder 15)
      - Curtis, John A., 1950-1952 (Container 51, folder 16)
      - Dukes, Jesse
        - 1952-1955
          - 1 of 2 (Container 52, folder 1)
          - 2 of 2 (Container 52, folder 2)
      - Dyer, Philip, 1953-1954 (Container 52, folder 3)
      - Everett, William, 1953-1954 (Container 52, folder 4)
      - Extradition
        - 1952 (Container 52, folder 5)
        - 1953 (Container 52, folder 6)
        - 1954 (Container 52, folder 7) (Box R9)
        - 1955-1957 (Container 52, folder 8)
      - Favors, Henry H., 1955-1958 (Container 52, folder 9)
      - Griffin, Willie, 1951-1954 (Container 52, folder 10)
      - Groveland, Fla., 1949-1954 (rape case and riots)
        - Contributions and expenses
          - 1950-1953 (Container 52, folder 12)
      - Harrison, Yancey, 1957-1958 (Container 54, folder 4)
      - High, Cleophus, 1953-1954 (Container 54, folder 7)
      - Holman, George, 1949-1954 (Container 54, folder 8)
      - Holt, Arthur, 1952 (Container 54, folder 9)
      - Hooper, Henry, 1961-1962 (Container 54, folder 10)
      - Horton, Jack, and Leola Marie Thomason, 1952 (Container 55, folder 1)
      - Hudson, James Willy, 1954-1955 (Container 55, folder 2)
      - Jackson, Alfred, 1951-1952 (Container 55, folder 3)
      - Keeton, L. C., 1948-1951 (Container 55, folder 4)
      - Love, Betty
      - Correspondence
        - 1949-1950 (Container 55, folder 8)
        - 1951 (Container 55, folder 9)
      - Marshall, William Authur
        - 1951-1952 (Container 55, folder 11)
        - 1953 (Container 55, folder 12)
      - McGregor, Charles, 1949-1955 (Container 56, folder 4) (Box R10)
      - McWhorter, Jesse, 1958-1962 (Container 56, folder 5)
      - Mills, Lawrence, 1953-1955 (Container 56, folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous cases
        - A
          - 1951-1954 (Container 57, folder 1)
          - 1955-1962 (Container 57, folder 2)
        - B
          - 1950-1952 (Container 57, folder 3)
          - 1953 (Container 57, folder 4)
          - 1954 (Container 57, folder 5)
          - 1955 (Container 57, folder 6)
          - 1956-1958 (Container 57, folder 7)
          - 1959-1962 (Container 57, folder 8)
        - C
          - 1950-1952 (Container 57, folder 9)
          - 1953 (Container 57, folder 10)
          - 1954 (Container 57, folder 11) (Box R11)
          - 1955 (Container 57, folder 12)
          - 1958-1962 (Container 57, folder 13)
        - D
          - 1950-1953 (Container 58, folder 1)
          - 1954-1955 (Container 58, folder 2)
        - E, 1951-1959 (Container 58, folder 3)
        - F
          - 1951-1952 (Container 58, folder 4)
          - 1953 (Container 58, folder 5)
          - 1954 (Container 58, folder 6)
          - 1955-1962 (Container 58, folder 7)
        - G
          - 1948-1951 (Container 58, folder 8)
          - 1952 (Container 58, folder 9)
          - 1953-1954 (Container 58, folder 10) (Box R12)
          - 1955 (Container 58, folder 11)
        - H
          - 1950-1951 (Container 59, folder 1)
          - 1952 (Container 59, folder 2)
          - 1953 (Container 59, folder 3)
          - 1954 (Container 59, folder 4)
          - 1955 (Container 59, folder 5)
          - 1957-1958 (Container 59, folder 6)
          - 1959-1962 (Container 59, folder 7)
        - I, 1953-1955 (Container 59, folder 8)
        - J
          - 1949-1951 (Container 59, folder 9)
          - 1952-1953 (Container 59, folder 10)
          - 1955 (Container 59, folder 11) (Box R13)
          - 1956-1957 (Container 60, folder 1)
          - 1958-1959 (Container 60, folder 2)
          - 1960-1962 (Container 60, folder 3)
        - K, 1951-1955 (Container 60, folder 4)
        - L, 1951-1959 (Container 60, folder 5)
        - M
          - 1951-1952 (Container 60, folder 6)
          - 1953 (Container 60, folder 7)
          - 1955, 1959
            - 1 of 2 (Container 60, folder 8)
            - 2 of 2 (Container 60, folder 9)
        - N, 1951-1961 (Container 60, folder 10)
        - O, 1955-1961 (Container 60, folder 11)
        - P
          - 1950-1952 (Container 61, folder 1)
          - 1953-1954 (Container 61, folder 2) (Box R14)
          - 1955-1956 (Container 61, folder 3)
          - 1957-1958 (Container 61, folder 4)
          - 1959-1962 (Container 61, folder 5)
        - R
          - 1950-1951 (Container 61, folder 6)
          - 1952-1953 (Container 61, folder 7)
          - 1955-1959 (Container 61, folder 8)
        - S
          - 1949-1952 (Container 61, folder 9)
          - 1953-1955 (Container 61, folder 10)
          - 1957-1958 (Container 61, folder 11)
          - 1959 (Container 61, folder 12)
          - 1960-1962 (Container 61, folder 13)
        - T
          - 1950-1951 (Container 62, folder 1)
          - 1952-1955 (Container 62, folder 2) (Box R15)
          - 1957 (Container 62, folder 3)
          - 1958-1961 (Container 62, folder 4)
        - U-V, 1950, 1959-1960 (Container 62, folder 5)
        - W
          - 1950-1951 (Container 62, folder 6)
          - 1952 (Container 62, folder 7)
          - 1957 (Container 62, folder 8)
          - 1958 (Container 62, folder 9)
          - 1959-1962 (Container 62, folder 10)
        - X-Y-Z, 1950-1951 (Container 62, folder 11)
      - Moore, David, 1959-1961 (Container 63, folder 1)
      - Moore, John B., 1953-1955 (Container 63, folder 2)
      - Mosley, Adam, 1954-1955 (Container 63, folder 3)
      - Myles, Willie E., 1954-1955 (Container 63, folder 4)
      - Palor, Ernest, 1951-1953 (Container 63, folder 6)
      - Parol
        - 1952 (Container 63, folder 7)
        - 1955 (Container 63, folder 8)
        - 1956 (Container 63, folder 9) (Box R16)
        - 1957-1959 (Container 63, folder 10)
      - Payne, Lonnie, 1953-1955 (Container 63, folder 11)
      - Perry, Albert E., 1958 (Container 63, folder 12)
      - Priester, Warren J., 1952-1955 (Container 65, folder 6)
      - Rape
        - Artes, Lula, 1951 (Container 65, folder 9)
        - Clark, Willie, 1940 (Container 65, folder 10)
        - Densmore, LaVenia, 1938-1941 (Container 65, folder 11)
        - Hamilton, Carl, 1949-1953 (Container 65, folder 13)
        - Higgs, James, 1952-1953 (Container 65, folder 14)
        - Jackson, Albert, 1951-1952 (Container 66, folder 5)
        - Martinsville Seven
          - Correspondence
            - 1949 (Container 66, folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous cases
          - 1951
            - 1 of 2 (Container 67, folder 7)
            - 2 of 2 (Container 67, folder 8)
          - 1952
            - 1 of 2 (Container 67, folder 9)
            - 2 of 2 (Container 67, folder 10)
          - 1953 (Box R17)
            - 1 of 2 (Container 67, folder 11)
            - 2 of 2 (Container 67, folder 12)
          - Smith, Wallace, 1952-1955 (Container 68, folder 5)
      - Ricks, Robert, 1955-1956 (Container 68, folder 6)
      - Saunders, Titus, 1955-1956 (Container 68, folder 7)
      - Sevilla, Caledonia, 1949-1951 (Container 68, folder 8)
      - Southall, Benjamin, 1949-1951 (Container 68, folder 9)
      - Summey, Cortland, 1951-1958 (Container 68, folder 11)
      - Teabout, Clarence, 1949-1951 (Container 68, folder 12)
      - Tootle, Fred, 1955 (Container 68, folder 14)
      - Ward, William Henry, 1949-1952 (Container 70, folder 4)
      - Way, Edward
        - 1947-1950 (Container 70, folder 10)
        - 1951, Jan. - June (Container 70, folder 11)
      - Williams, Earl, 1958-1959 (Container 71, folder 2)
      - Williams, John, 1956-1960 (Container 71, folder 3)
      - Williams, Louis, 1947-1951 (Container 71, folder 4)
      - Williams, Lucille, 1956-1960 (Container 71, folder 5)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1954-1955 (Container 71, folder 6)
    - Extradition
      - Miscellaneous cases, 1949-1951
        - 1 of 2 (Container 83, folder 6)
        - 2 of 2 (Container 83, folder 7) (Box R18)
    - Immigration
      - Cases
        - 1948-1951 (Container 96, folder 1)
        - 1952-1954 (Container 96, folder 2)
      - Miscellany, 1949-1954, undated (Container 96, folder 3)
    - Juries
      - Asheville, N.C., Sigmon case, 1939-1940 (Container 97, folder 7)
    - Korea, defense fund
      - Contributions, 1951
        - 1 of 5 (Container 99, folder 10)
        - 2 of 5 (Container 99, folder 11)
        - 3 of 5 (Container 99, folder 12)
        - 4 of 5 (Container 99, folder 13)
        - 5 of 5 (Container 99, folder 14) (Box R19)
    - Labor
      - Cameron, Henry L., 1952-1956 (Container 102, folder 8)
      - Civil service
        - Cook, Margarette, 1944-1952 (Container 102, folder 10)
        - Vann, Edith, 1957-1960 (Container 102, folder 12)
      - Correspondence
        - A, 1950-1955 (Container 104, folder 1)
        - B, 1950-1956 (Container 104, folder 2)
        - C, 1951-1956 (Container 104, folder 3)
        - D, 1950-1958 (Container 104, folder 4)
        - E, 1950-1955 (Container 104, folder 5)
        - G, 1951-1954 (Container 104, folder 6)
        - H, 1950-1955 (Container 104, folder 7)
        - J, 1951-1955 (Container 104, folder 8) (Box R20)
        - K, 1949-1956 (Container 104, folder 9)
        - M, 1950-1956 (Container 104, folder 10)
        - O, 1951-1955 (Container 104, folder 11)
        - R, 1950-1954 (Container 105, folder 1)
        - S, 1950-1955 (Container 105, folder 2)
        - T-V, 1951-1955 (Container 105, folder 3)
        - W, 1951-1957 (Container 105, folder 4)
      - Customs bureaus, 1947-1952 (Container 105, folder 5)
      - Reynolds, Mary Lee, 1954 (Container 109, folder 6)
      - Rutherford, Alvin, 1950-1952 (Container 109, folder 7)
      - Unions
        - Hughes, Orville, 1947-1954 (Container 110, folder 2)
    - Masons, Prince Hall Grand Lodge, Legal Research Fund (Box R21)
      - Financial records
        - Memoranda, 1951-1956 (Container 113, folder 4)
        - Reports, 1951-1957 (Container 113, folder 5)
    - Miller, Moses L., 1954 (Container 113, folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence
      - B, 1950-1952 (Container 114, folder 7)
      - C
        - 1955-1957 (Container 115, folder 5)
        - 1958 (Container 115, folder 6)
        - 1959 (Container 115, folder 7)
        - 1960 (Container 115, folder 8)
        - 1961 (Container 115, folder 9)
      - D
        - 1951-1955 (Container 116, folder 1)
        - 1958-1959 (Container 116, folder 3)
        - 1960-1961 (Container 116, folder 4)
      - E, 1951-1960 (Container 116, folder 5) (Box R22)
      - F
        - 1952-1957 (Container 116, folder 6)
        - 1958 (Container 116, folder 7)
        - 1959 (Container 116, folder 8)
        - 1960 (Container 116, folder 9)
      - G
        - 1951-1957 (Container 117, folder 1)
        - 1958-1959 (Container 117, folder 2)
        - 1961, undated (Container 117, folder 4)
      - H
        - 1949-1954 (Container 117, folder 5)
        - 1955 (Container 117, folder 6)
        - 1956-1958 (Container 117, folder 7) (Box R23)
        - 1959 (Container 117, folder 8)
        - 1960, undated (Container 118, folder 1)
      - I, 1954-1960 (Container 118, folder 2)
      - J
        - 1950-1954 (Container 118, folder 3)
        - 1955 (Container 118, folder 4)
        - 1957-1961 (Container 118, folder 5)
        - 1962-1963 (Container 118, folder 6)
      - K
        - 1950-1958 (Container 118, folder 7)
        - 1959-1960 (Container 118, folder 8) (Box R24)
      - L
        - 1951-1955 (Container 118, folder 9)
        - 1957-1959 (Container 119, folder 1)
        - 1960 (Container 119, folder 2)
      - M
        - 1951-1954 (Container 119, folder 3)
        - 1955-1957 (Container 119, folder 4)
        - 1958 (Container 119, folder 5)
        - 1959 (Container 119, folder 6)
        - 1960-1961 (Container 119, folder 7)
      - N, 1951-1960, undated (Container 119, folder 8) (Box R25)
      - O, 1951-1960 (Container 120, folder 1)
      - P
        - 1951-1957 (Container 120, folder 2)
        - 1958 (Container 120, folder 3)
        - 1959 (Container 120, folder 4)
        - 1960-1961 (Container 120, folder 5)
      - R
        - 1951-1957 (Container 120, folder 7)
        - 1958 (Container 120, folder 8)